Guide to the Whitman College Dean of Students records
Whitman College and Northwest Archives
Whitman College Dean of Students records
1946-2015
Whitman College and Northwest Archives
Whitman College
WCA.048
15.5 linear feet 14 record cartons, 2 document boxes, 1 flat box
The Dean of Students records contains materials related to student affairs, student services, and the governance and guidance of student life at Whitman.
Materials in this collection are closed for 20 years from the date of creation. Student educational records such as credentials, grade sheets, correspondence, reports, notes, applications, and all other records pertaining to past and present students are governed by the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act of 1974 and are restricted for 75 years from the date of creation. Personnel related files of the college's faculty and staff, including search, review, promotion, reappointment, tenure, and disciplinary/grievance records, are restricted for 75 years from the date of creation. Additional restrictions may apply to other materials in this collection.
The collection spans the years 1946 to 2015 and includes the records of deans Robert Whitner, Gordon Scribner, Russell DeRemer, Rob Gardner, and Chuck Cleveland. The collection also contains the records of Associate Dean of Students, Assistant Dean of Students, and limited records from the Dean of Men and the Dean of Women. The collection is divided into five series: 1. Committees, 2. Dean of Students, 3. Fraternities and Sororities, 4. Housing and Residence Life, and 5. Office of Student Affairs.
The Committees series dates from 1975 to 2007, and contains meeting minutes and memoranda of the various groups which guide and govern student life, such as the College Council on Interpersonal Relations. The Dean of Students series dates from 1946 to 2015, and contains memoranda and correspondence, policy statements, annual reports and budgets, and other planning documents. The Fraternities and Sororities series dates from 1963-2005, and contains memoranda, correspondence, rush statistics, and policy documents relating to Greek Life at Whitman. The Housing and Residence Life series dates from 1950 to 2009, and contains policy documents, occupancy reports, and memoranda and correspondence relating to the staffing and maintenance of dorms, interest houses, and Greek houses. The Office of Student Affairs series dates from 1948 to 2009, and contains advising manuals, annual reports, and student services records. The series also includes meeting minutes, correspondence, and policy documents of the Associated Students of Whitman College and the Council on Student Affairs.
The Dean of Students is responsible for guiding student life, and serves as the Vice President of Student Affairs. They mentor, advocate, and advise individual students, as well as student groups. The Dean of Students reports to the President of the college.
The Dean of Students was established around 1965. The role of the new dean was to more efficiently and effectively guide and govern student affairs and student services, duties which had previously been shared by a board of deans. In the late 1960s and early 1970s, after years of student advocacy, Dean of Students Gordon Scribner coordinated the liberalization of many rules and social regulations governing student life. When Scribner transitioned to Director of Alumni Affairs in 1978, the Office of Student Affairs went through a massive restructuring, incorporating into the office of the Dean of Students. At this time, the Dean of Students' duties included "the supervision, direction, and coordination of student services, including the food service, the Student Center, financial advising, career planning and placement, residential life, student activities, personal counseling, and health services." The Dean of Students would also serve as chair of the Council on Student Affairs.
Chronology of the position:
Robert Whitner (circa 1965-1967)
Gordon Scriber (1967-1978)
Russell DeRemer (1978-1994)
Chuck Cleveland (1994-2017)
Kazi Joshua (2017-)
The collection is arranged into five series: 1. Committees, 2. Dean of Students, 3. Fraternities and Sororities, 4. Housing and Residence Life, and 5. Office of Student Affairs. Materials within each series are arranged alphabetically.
Scribner, Gordon; DeRemer, Russell J.; Whitner, Robert L.; Cleveland, Charles (Chuck)
Colleges and Universities; Student Life
- Committees, 1975-2007
  - Advising, 1984-1994 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - AIDS committee, 1 of 2, 1987-1993 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - AIDS committee, 2 of 2, 1987-1993 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Americans with Disabilities Act [ADA] committee, 1990-1993 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Americans with Disabilities Act [ADA] committee, 1990-1993 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Americans with Disabilities Act [ADA] committee, 1990-1993 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Annual report of the committee on academic advising of minority students 1974-1975, 1975 May 6 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - College bookstore advisory committee, 1981-1994 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - College Council on Interpersonal Relations [CCIR], 1 of 2, 1985-1993 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - College Council on Interpersonal Relations [CCIR], 2 of 2, 1985-1993 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Conservation committee, 1994 July 13 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Council on sexual misconduct [Folder restricted until 2027], 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Council on sexual misconduct training [Folder restricted until 2027], 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Diversity task force, 1 of 2, 1989-1991 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Diversity task force, 2 of 2, 1989-1991 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Diversity task force, 1997-2000 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Diversity task force, 1 of 2 [Folder restricted until 2024], 2001-2004 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Diversity task force, 2 of 2 [Folder restricted until 2024], 2001-2004 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Diversity task force, 1 of 2 [Folder restricted until 2025], 2004-2005 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Diversity task force, 2 of 2 [Folder restricted until 2025], 2004-2005 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Diversity task force, 1 of 4 [Folder restricted until 2025], 2005 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Diversity task force, 2 of 4 [Folder restricted until 2025], 2005 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Diversity task force, 3 of 4 [Folder restricted until 2025], 2005 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Diversity task force, 4 of 4 [Folder restricted until 2025], 2005 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Diversity task force, 1 of 3 [Folder restricted until 2026], 2006 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Diversity task force, 2 of 3 [Folder restricted until 2026], 2006 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Diversity task force, 3 of 3 [Folder restricted until 2026], 2006 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Diversity task force [Folder restricted until 2027], 2007 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Freshman life/opening week committee, 1 of 2, 1986-1993 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Freshman life/opening week committee, 2 of 2, 1986-1993 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Overseers student life committee meeting, 1995 September 22-1995 November 6 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Overseers student life committee meeting, 1 of 2, 1996 February 22-1996 December 10 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Overseers student life committee meeting, 2 of 2, 1996 February 22-1996 December 10 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Overseers student life committee meeting materials, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Overseers student life committee meeting materials, 1 of 2, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Overseers student life committee meeting materials, 2 of 2, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Overseers student life committee meeting materials, 1 of 2, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Overseers student life committee meeting materials, 2 of 2, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Overseers student life committee meeting materials, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Personnel advisory committee, 1 of 2, 1981-1995 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Personnel advisory committee, 2 of 2, 1981-1995 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Policy committee, 1 of 2, 1978-1996 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Policy committee, 2 of 2, 1978-1996 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Prison research committee, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Rush [fraternities and sororities] committee, 1 of 3, 1984-1999 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Rush [fraternities and sororities] committee, 2 of 3, 1984-1999 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Rush [fraternities and sororities] committee, 3 of 3, 1984-1999 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Statement of the Committee on Academic Aspects of Racial Minority Enrollment, 1971-02-03T00:00:00+00:00 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Student financial services committee, 1982-1992 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Student life committee, 1 of 2, 1989-1999 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Student life committee, 2 of 2, 1989-1999 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Student life committee, 1 of 2, 1991-1994 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Student union committee, 1 of 2, 1978-1995 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Student union committee, 2 of 2, 1978-1995 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Studies involving human subjects committee [Folder restricted until 2023], 1997-2003 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Substance abuse committee, 1 of 2, 1990-1993 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Substance abuse committee, 2 of 2, 1990-1993 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Whitman student alcohol attitude survey [Alcohol Use Committee], 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Dean of Students, 1946-2015
  - 3-2 Engineering program, 1952-1973 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - A Planned Approach to College, circa 1960 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - AAUP [Association of American University Professors], 1975-1983 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - AAHE [American Association for Higher Education], 1 of 3, 1980-1985 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - AAHE [American Association for Higher Education], 2 of 3, 1980-1985 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - AAHE [American Association for Higher Education], 3 of 3, 1980-1985 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Academic calendar, 1 of 2, 1969-1995 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Academic calendar, 2 of 2, 1969-1995 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Academic calendar revisions, 1987-1994 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - [Academic Council] memoranda, 1 of 3, 1989-1994 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - [Academic Council] memoranda, 2 of 3 [Partial contents restricted until 2067], 1989-1994 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - [Academic Council] memoranda, 3 of 3, 1989-1994 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Academic recognition banquet, 1974-1988 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - ACE [American Council on Education], 1 of 6, 1979-1993 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - ACE [American Council on Education], 2 of 6, 1979-1993 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - ACE [American Council on Education], 3 of 6, 1979-1993 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - ACE [American Council on Education], 4 of 6, 1979-1993 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - ACE [American Council on Education], 5 of 6, 1979-1993 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - ACE [American Council on Education], 6 of 6, 1979-1993 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - ACT [American College Testing], 1981-1993 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Activities control system, 1946 July 9 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Addresses miscellaneous, 1988-1991 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Administrative organization of Whitman College, 1947-1994 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Administrative retreat, 1 of 3, 1980-1989 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Administrative retreat, 2 of 3, 1980-1989 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Administrative retreat, 3 of 3, 1980-1989 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Administrative staff status [Partial contents restricted until 2064], 1978-1989 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Admissions: Alumni children, teachers, circa 1955 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Admissions: ASWC [Associated Students of Whitman College] admissions committee [Partial contents restricted until 2030], circa 1955 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Admissions: Athletes program for football teams, 1954-1955 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Admissions: Creative student questionnaire and memoranda [Folder restricted until 2038], 1962-1963 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Admissions: "The Admissions Muddle", 1958 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Admissions: [Inland Empire] Science Fair, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Admissions: Visitation worksheets, Saturday statistics, 1953-1960 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Alcohol [on campus, including research, surveys, and correspondence], 1 of 2, 1986-1993 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Alcohol [on campus, including research, surveys, and correspondence], 2 of 2, 1986-1993 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Alcoholic beverage procedure form, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - [Alfred P.] Sloan Conference, 1959-1961 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Alumni Office, 1989-1993 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Annual report, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Annual report, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Annual report, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Annual report, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Annual report, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Annual report, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Annual report, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Annual report, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Annual report, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Annual report, Assistant Dean of Women, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Annual report, Assistant Dean of Men, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Annual report, Assistant Dean of Students, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Annual report, Assistant Dean of Students, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Annual report, Associate Dean of Students, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Annual report, Associate Dean of Students, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Annual report, Career Center, 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Annual report, Dean of Men, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Annual report, Dean of Women, 1927-1960; 1960 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Annual report (draft), 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Annual report, governing boards, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Annual report, Religious Counselor, 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Annual report, Religious Counselor, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Annual Title IX report, 2014-2015 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Approved budgets, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Approved budgets, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Approved budgets, 1 of 2 [Folder restricted until 2023], 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Approved budgets, 2 of 2 [Folder restricted until 2023], 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Articles and clippings, 1 of 2, 1980-1994 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Articles and clippings, 2 of 2, 1980-1994 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Articles and clippings regarding student protests around the United States, 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Aryan Nations [Hayden Lake, Idaho, posters distruted on campus], circa 1985 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Assistant Dean of Students: Judicial reports, 1987-1995 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Assistant Dean of Students: Job description [transition from Sally Click to Maggie McGrew], 1989-1991 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Assistant Dean of Students: Report of student activities, 1987-1989 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Associate Dean of Students: Photograph, circa 1979-1982 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Associate Dean of Students: Department statistical reports [miscellaneous], circa 1986-1993 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Athletics, 1982-1994 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Attrition and retention study, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Attrition at Whitman: An Exploration 1980-1981 by Richard N. Jacks Ph.D. (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Awards correspondence, 1979-1994 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Awards correspondence [with recipients and donors], 1950-1961 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Awards: International Nickel, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Awards: Lincoln Lumber Company scholarship [for citizens of the Confederated Tribes of the Colville Reservation], 1954 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Awards: Preprofessional and activity scholarships, 1937-1950 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Awards: Quiz Kids & PTA, 1943-1947 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Awards: Standard Oil scholarships [Folder restricted until 2030], 1954-1955 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Awards: Union-Bulletin scholarships [Partial contents restricted until 2032], 1952-1964 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Awards: Washington State Resources, 1951-1952 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Baker Faculty Center, 1980-1993 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Battelle/Whitman College Cooperative Science program, 1979-1981 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Board of Review memoranda [Partial contents restricted until 2054], 1967-1989 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Bookstore (student center), 1980-1994 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Budget memorandum and electronic funds pamphlets, 1979, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Budget preparation, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Budget preparation, 1 of 3, 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Budget preparation, 2 of 3, 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Budget preparation, 3 of 3, 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Budget preparation, 1 of 2, 1999-2001 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Budget preparation, 2 of 2, 1999-2001 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Budget preparation, 1 of 3, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Budget preparation, 2 of 3, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Budget preparation, 3 of 3, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Budget preparation, 1 of 5 [Folder restricted until 2023], 2002-2003 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Budget preparation, 2 of 5 [Folder restricted until 2023], 2002-2003 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Budget preparation, 3 of 5 [Folder restricted until 2023], 2002-2003 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Budget preparation, 4 of 5 [Folder restricted until 2023], 2002-2003 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Budget preparation, 5 of 5 [Folder restricted until 2023], 2002-2002 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Budget preparation [Folder restricted until 2024], 2003-2004 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Budget preparation, 1 of 2 [Folder restricted until 2026], 2005-2006 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Budget preparation, 2 of 2 [Folder restricted until 2026], 2005-2006 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Budget preparation, 1 of 2 [Folder restricted until 2027], 2006-2007 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Budget preparation, 2 of 2 [Folder restricted until 2027], 2006-2007 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Business cards, 1987-1992 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Campus compact [service learning], 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - "Campus Conference on Religion, Whitman College" [program], 1959 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - "Campus Conference on Religion, Whitman College" [program and letter of objection], circa 1960 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Campus ministry [correspondence with Reverend Larry V. Gaffin], 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Campus Security Act [Partial contents restricted until 2066], 1990-1993 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Campus signage [memoranda], 1991 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Career center ["Examining Ourselves Through Their Eyes: A report on focus groups in the Whitman Career Center"], 1990-1991 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Career center memoranda, 1990-1993 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - CASE [Council for Advancement and Support of Education], 1988-1992 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Cell groups [calls for faculty and staff participation], 1969-1978 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Cell groups [memoranda and calls for participation], 1986-1991 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Cell groups/Student Life Groups, call for participation, 1973 September (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Certificates of Achievement, circa 1982 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Chaperone policy, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Children's Home Society [Board of Trustees materials], 1987-1993 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - College cabin, 1976-1992 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - College catalog, 1979-1993 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - College facilities, Old Music Building, 1989-1992 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - College facilities, use and maintenance, 1991-1994 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - CSS [College Scholarship Service, reports, memoranda, and procedures] [Partial contents restricted until 2034], 1954-1955 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - CSS [College Scholarship Service, reports, memoranda, and procedures] [Partial contents restricted until 2034], 1956-1957 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - CSS [College Scholarship Service, reports, memoranda, and procedures] [Partial contents restricted until 2033], 1958-1959 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - CSS [College Scholarship Service, reports, memoranda, and procedures] [Partial contents restricted until 2034], 1959 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - CSS [College Scholarship Service, reports, memoranda, and procedures] [Partial contents restricted until 2036], 1960-1965 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - College vehicles use policy [and memoranda], 1980-1993 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Commencement programs, 1 of 2, 1985-1994 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Commencement programs, 2 of 2, 1985-1995 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Community service/Walla Walla relations, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Comparative statistics, Whitman versus other schools, 1990-1992 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Computer Services, student information database planning, 1990-1993 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - "Computing at Whitman College", 1994 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Contracting [electronic systems], 1993 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Convocation, 1 of 2, 1960-1993 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Convocation, 2 of 2, 1960-1993 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence concerning student discipline, 1922-1930 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence with parents and others outside of Whitman, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Department statistical reports, 1986-1996 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Department of Health, Education, and Welfare, Nationwide Health Plan Survey, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - [DeRemer] Christmas cards and party, 1978-1993 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Directory information, 1990-1993 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - C [Delegation from Sechuan University, Fulbright scholarship materials, Choral Contest award], 1980-1993 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Dress code [Dalton School], 1969 December 18 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Drug-free schools and workplace, 1978-1992 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Education Information Service: College Attendance Costs and Scholarships, 1960 December (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Educational Testing Service grade prediction, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - ETS [Educational Testing Service] programs, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Emergency procedures, 1982-1994 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Employee salaries and contracts, 1980-1996 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - End of year reports, 1988-1992 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Entering Students, Non-returning Students, and the IGI: A Report on Institutional Research, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - F [freshman information, foreign study], 1992 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Faculty development, 1991-1994 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Faculty evaluations [procedures and evaluation criteria] [Partial contents restricted until 2063], 1980-1988 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Faculty forum, 1990-1993 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Faculty handbook [drafting sections on various campus offices], 1987 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Faculty [memoranda], 1 of 3, 1982-1992 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Faculty [memoranda], 2 of 3, 1982-1992 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Faculty [memoranda], 3 of 3, 1982-1992 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Faculty orientation, 1987-1990 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Faire magazine, 1982-1987 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Federal requirements [according to campus office], 1992 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Financial development: Foundations and grants, 1 of 2, 1985-1993 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Financial development: Foundations and grants, 2 of 2 [Partial contents restricted until 2068], 1985-1993 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Fire inspection reports, 1985-1992 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Fiske Guide to Colleges, Barron's [Best Buys in College Education] and Peterson's [Annual Survey of Higher Education Personnel], 1989-1994 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Freshman Advisors Handbook, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - G [General Education], 1982 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Garrett scholarship, 1976-1992 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Gay/Lesbian Association, 1991-1992 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - General Studies, new Freshman Core, 1979, bulk 1990-1994 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Grants, Steele-Reese Foundation scholarship, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Grants, 1 of 2, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Grants, 2 of 2, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Grants, FIPSE [The Fund for the Improvement of Postsecondary Education], 1 of 2, 1991-1993 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Grants, FIPSE [The Fund for the Improvement of Postsecondary Education], 2 of 2, 1991-1993 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Grants, Mexican-American outreach program, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Grants, National Science Foundation, 1991-1992 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Grievance procedure for students [student records policy] (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - H [Harvard Educational Review, history lectureship, honor societies], 1981 (Box 6, Folder 32)